I see.
I just have one question for you.
What kind of lunatic
adopts a water monster?
Well there, don't call her that.
She's not a monster, she's
my baby and my familiar.
I admit I was frightened of
the creature at first too,
but it's actually quite
a docile little thing.
Docile monsters do not exist!
Or have you forgotten the
chaos we just endured?
I have not, but Ralaire's a
total sweetheart, I promise.
Wait just a moment, what is Ray Lair?
Don't tell me you named that abomination!
After you and me, of course.
Ray plus Claire equals Ray Lair!
You would disgrace my name by
bestowing it upon that menace!
Oh, stop it, it's cute!
She's like the root of our love.
If that's what you think,
then that's all the more reason
to have Professor Torrid kill it!
Please don't do that, Miss Claire!
Ray Lair's a good girl!
She even knows how to do tricks!
Sit.
Lay down.
Roll over!
So smart!
What do you mean, smart?
It barely moved!
That's it, I'm telling the professor!
No, wait!
You haven't seen the best part!
Alright, girl. Ready?
It's go time.
Now, undeen!
It's me!
In miniature!
When a water slime is in the
presence of a beautiful lady,
it will often assume her form, like so.
My, is that really true?
Sure!
Kinda sorta halfway true.
They actually just mimic the
shape of whatever's nearby.
It's a type of camouflage they
use to protect themselves.
No harm in Miss Claire believing
the beautiful lady part, though.
What a fascinating ability.
I suppose it is rather endearing.
Got him!
Oh, very well then.
I will not have the
creature done away with,
but in return you are responsible
for teaching it proper discipline.
Thank you very kindly, my queen.
It shall be done post-haste.
And no sneaking about.
You'll reveal its existence to everyone.
Okay.
Lastly, the name Ray
Laher simply won't do.
You'll need to come up with a new one.
Oh, ship sailed on that one, I'm afraid.
Meaning what? Well, um,
a familiar never forgets its name, so once
you give it one, there's no going back.
This little cutie will forever
be known, Ezreal! I object!
With my whole heart and soul!
The reason why I'm so proud to be born.
Everyone, you don't
want to think the truth?
It's not a lie, happy end!
It's a lie, empty sentence.
I can't believe it's true.
I think I'm true, I like you who?
I'm not an angelic, I'm not a fool.
I can't believe it, you like you, you!
I don't want to be a fool.
I don't want to give up
until I think about it.
It's a fun game, I love you!
Am I kidding?
I adore you in ice cream mode.
That is quite enough out of you!
You ladies passed, I take it?
Of course, this was just the written exam.
They say the practical's what matters.
Hope you're ready.
For a bit of recap,
the Academy Knights are self-governed
organization within the school.
Like student council, but fancier.
It's an elite group.
Only those who pass the rigorous
entrance exams are admitted.
And the competition is mega fierce.
You took the exam as well, Misha?
I had no idea you were interested
in joining the knights.
Miss Claire asked me to apply for a spot.
She said Ray needed a guardian.
That makes sense.
Commoner, I want a rematch.
If you fail today's practical
exam, you will leave this academy.
Again, I do not want to.
And again, I insist you think it
over for more than one second!
Ugh, fine, if that's what you want.
Why don't we compete under the same
terms as last time to keep it simple?
Do you think I'm a fool?
You're trying to deceive
me again, you trickster!
Oh, shucks, you remembered, huh?
Alright, how about we just
agree if I fail, then you win?
And if I pass, then I win,
nice and straightforward.
Wouldn't it be more straightforward
to say that if I pass, I win?
That puts me at too great a disadvantage.
We both know you're going
to pass with flying colors!
Well, seems you aren't totally oblivious.
All right, if you win, then what?
You agreed to do one thing I say, just
like you did in our previous arrangement.
Are you there?
Hey!
You're supposed to stay putt!
Oh, is this the familiar
I've been hearing about?
Oh, it's adorable!
If you pass the first test, well done!
That's the knight's captain, Lorek.
The other guy is his vice-captain.
Now moving on to Phase 2.
Head on outside for the practical exam.
Welcome to today's main event, recruits.
It's time for one-on-one mock battles.
There are ten rounds, and our survey says
the most anticipated are the first battle,
Bane Bauer vs. Hugh Bauer.
The 6th battle, Rod Bauer vs.
Misha Jor And the 10th
battle, Claire Francois vs.
Ray Taylor
This special barrier will reduce
the amount of damage taken.
So no holding back, fight with all
your strength and no reservations!
Now then, will our first
combatants please step forward?
Do try and go easy on
me, won't you, Thane?
Be safe, Prince Dane.
Be safe, Prince U. Prince V.
Prince action is a great
way to open the show.
Combatants ready?
Begin!
Looks like Prince Dane
is on the offensive.
He's an advanced user of wind magic.
He takes an attribute
normally used for support?
and manipulates it to boost his strength.
in the style of a magic warrior.
I know you want to win,
but try not to be reckless.
That can lead to mistakes.
And you wouldn't want to hurt your
precious baby brother now, would you?
Keep talking.
Water!
Yeah!
Prince Yu is so versatile
with his attribute.
He's using the water to
deflect Prince Thane's attacks.
I think it's time we put
some distance between us.
If he tries to get near,
he'll slip on the ice.
That's bad news for a close-range
fighter like Prince Thane.
Now then, I believe
it's my turn to counter.
An intermediate water magic user,
Prince Yu has more than a
few tricks up his sleeve.
It's no wonder people
call him the Ice Prince.
And go!
Prince Thane, look!
Prince Thane deflects the
icicles with a wall of wind.
And now a charge, head
on towards his opponent.
Surely he'll slip on the ice.
No, he's compressing the
air and walking on it.
Impressive.
Ice filler!
Prince Thane is trapped
in a prison of ice.
His windwall won't help
him out of this one.
All these shards.
I yield the match.
The first battle is over.
The winner is Prince Thane.
You make for a worthy
opponent as always, brother.
You do as well, though
I suspect you held back.
You use ice and water,
but no healing magic.
Oh, Prince Fane, you're so gallant.
Everybody looks cool in a magic battle.
Five battles down, on to the sixth.
All right, sick of Misha.
Well, here we go.
Goodness, she's not very enthused, is she?
Can't say I really blame her.
I mean who would be excited
about going up against Prince
Rod don't hold back Misha I
wish you the very best of luck.
You're gonna need it.
Thank you for this opportunity Prince
Rod Jeez, you don't need to be so polite.
We're dueling
Fine, I'll just force you to do
your best if that's what it takes.
Come on!
Hope you don't mind some extra company?
Meet my minions.
The Flame Troops!
There are so many!
Aw, they're cute! Attack!
The Minions have taken the field!
Things look dire for Misha!
How will she respond?
Was that sound? Wait, what?
The Minions have all disappeared!
What in the world did she do?
That noise!
It was like fingernails on a chalkboard!
You heard it as well, right?
Mm-hmm.
Misha wields her wind magic offensively,
channeling it into a sound
to strike her chosen target.
The technique is called siren.
Clever trick.
All right.
How about this?
Attack!
And burst!
What immense firepower!
But I don't see how she
can come back from this.
Misha!
Amazing!
She appears completely unscathed!
Was that another wind
magic technique? Yep.
It's called vacuum ripship!
She creates gaps in the
space around her to shut out
heat and insulate herself
from the prince's fire magic.
Basically, it's the same principle
that makes a thermos work.
Wow, good one.
You're tougher than I expected. Not bad.
He's attacked!
Prince Rod unleashes a barrage of minions!
One strike after another, classic Rod.
Such a show off.
Prince Rod's aptitude for fire
magic is only intermediate,
but he has an exceptional
amount of magic power.
For a match between students, he
seems to be taking things a bit far.
Agreed.
if he keeps this up.
I yield the match.
We have a victor! Misha!
Why did she collapse like that?
Low oxygen. What?
Prince Rod's nonstop attacks
and her continuous use
of vacuum rupture depleted
her body of the oxygen.
it needs to function properly.
To put it simply,
Misha was overwhelmed by the sheer
volume of magic he threw at her.
Misha, are you okay?
I'll be fine, but thank you.
You went too far, brother. Did I?
We should take her to the nurse's office.
Well, folks, this year's mat exam may be
the most exciting one we've ever seen.
And there's still one battle left.
You're going to win this for sure, Ms.
Blair! Yeah!
You're not coming or what you're made of!
Looks like we're in for
a pretty good show here.
Combatants ready!
The 10th battle is Claire
Francois versus Ray Taylor!
Prepare yourself, hooray, Taylor.
When we're done here, I will
personally read you your last rites.
Sounds great.
You and me duking it out should be fun.
Fun, did you say?
Yes, I suppose so.
If a humiliating defeat
is your idea of leisure...
The day's final battle starts now!
Well, that's odd.
Neither of the combatants are moving.
Do something!
It's not a contest if
you just stand there.
Oh, but the view from here is so lovely,
I can't bring myself to look away.
Cease your mockery and
fight me, you cretin!
Well, well.
Waiting on a little old
me to make the first move?
Say no more!
Ray has summoned a rock wall,
completely encasing her opponent.
Quite the effective barrier.
I'll show you.
She broke the rock? No, wait!
She appears to have melted it!
Whoa, nice one.
Takes some real heat to do that.
I know the fire attribute
is strong against Earth,
but even so, I didn't
realize it could melt it.
Well, I guess I'll have
to up my game a bit.
No, you don't!
A shield made entirely of fire?
Since flames aren't solid,
a wall of them isn't usually
effective as a means of defense.
But if they're hot enough to melt stone
instantly, that changes everything.
Her style of controlling
and expertly manipulating
fire is why Miss Claire is
known as the Red Lotus Queen.
If you're quite finished,
I believe it's my turn.
Now, behold the artistic
magic of a noble! Please!
Roar more!
Wow, no way.
She's using flamelands?
Whoa, is it hot in here?
Your magic is a work of art
just like you are, Miss Claire.
Will you shut up?
Sorry, can't do that.
Such a fool.
I'll melt through this flimsy
wall just like the others.
How did you...
Looks like it's made up a different
material than the last one was.
But what could have forstood that attack?
Tungsten carbide, my friend.
It's about twice as strong as steel,
and its melting point is
over 2,000 degrees Celsius.
I've got all this knowledge
from my previous life.
Might as well use it.
I must admit, unlike your character,
your craft is quite disciplined.
And yet, I'm afraid you're
still no match for me!
Looks like Claire is using
flamelance once again.
But this time she's going
bigger! Much bigger!
It's time to put an end to this!
Look at that twerp!
It's over.
From flamelance into a fireball fuselage!
What a remarkable control technique!
Rey shot down every one!
She's still putting up a good fight!
She managed to get every single
one with that little time to react?
With no missteps at all. How odd.
It's as if she anticipated
all of Claire's moves. Well?
Yeah, of course she did.
Rey spends every waking moment
thinking about her beloved Miss Claire!
Yeah, not even gonna try to deny that one.
I've memorized every last lovely
detail of Miss Claire's combat style.
Bested by a commoner.
Admiring my work?
Or are you giving up already?
Not a chance!
My apologies, Prince Rod.
Interesting.
It seems she's copying
your fire troop minions.
Attack!
The wall appears to be holding
against this latest barrage.
I see why she'd want to copy me,
but Claire doesn't have the magic
power to keep that up for very long.
I don't imagine that will be an issue.
If her tactic is what I suspect,
she's seeking to deprive Ray of oxygen,
in which case she will not need long.
Ray continues to focus on defense.
Aha!
Defense becomes offense.
If Claire can't escape,
that'll be the match.
Yeah, as if I would fall
for the same trick twice!
Now she's busting out the gymnastics!
Intelligence and
athleticism in one package.
I love herself!
I don't know what you're planning to do
from up there, but I can't wait to find out!
Impudent wretch, you're too
cocky for your own good.
I never imagined I would deploy
this against a mere commoner.
Wait!
That's the Francois Family Crest!
Magic Ray!
Huh? Huh?
That was only a warning shot.
As you can see, Magic Ray is far
stronger than my other techniques.
So much so that even I can
only wield it so many times.
You would be wise to surrender.
It's true that I probably can't dodge that
once I see it starting so you yield then,
you know?
Sorry, but stubbornness
is my biggest pitfall!
That's not good.
Honestly of all the spells you could use
you pick that one one more for giggles!
Once was undignified and now?
Hey down there, you think
you can make it out?
Yes, and you're going
to be sorry when I do!
Just wait, I can easily widen this hole
using magic - It's time to give up, Claire.
Prince Thane?
But why should I surrender
when I'm still able to fight?
Think for a moment.
Have you forgotten that
Rey is a dual caster?
And yet, she hasn't used
her water magic at all.
Even though it would have been much
more effective against your fire.
You've been holding back
the entire battle? Yeah.
Mocking me again, you
- Away, sorry ladies,
but given the situation I must step
in and call the match to a halt!
The winner is Ray Taylor!
You're an inspiration to us all!
As before, the results of the exam
will be Posted on the bulletin board!
If your name is listed,
then you've made the cut!
The newest members of The knights
are Prince Rod, Prince Yu,
Prince Dane, the commoner,
Misha, and me!
Oh, did I forget to tell you how
the practical exam is scored?
What counts in your
evaluation is raw talent.
Whether you win or lose has
no bearing on the result.
You're joking.
Congratulations!
I can't wait to see what you
two do when you work together.
Just try not to burn down the school.
So looks like I will.
Mmm, fine!
But the deal was that
you only get one request.
What do you demand this time?
Oh, not much.
Just promise me again
that you won't give up.
Wait, I don't understand
what you're playing at.
That's the exact same
thing you wanted before.
It sure is, so go ahead.
Swear it again, and we're even.
Well, alright.
I suppose that's fine.
I hereby swear before God that I,
Claire Francois, will never give up.
No matter what happens,
I will not abandon hope.
And I promise to continue
fighting until the end.
Are you truly certain that's all? Yes!
Hold on.
Why do I feel like there's
something I'm forgetting?
What am I to do with this?
Thank you.
come on forever I'm not even in a girl
I'm just cute I'm not
even in a girl I'm just
trying to get the look
I'm not even in a girl
I'm not even in a girl Thank you
It's a lot of lyrics in my life I'm not
even in a girl I'm not even in a girl
I'm not even in a girl
Miss Claire, Ray, congratulations
on getting into the Academy Nights.
But there is something you
should know about one of them.
Now we'll be together even
more often, Miss Claire.
I'll have to speak to Captain Lawrence.
I wasn't finished.